Dmytro Ostapenko

Middle Full-stack Application Developer (Kosice, Slovakia)

dostapenko82@gmail.com +1 424 206 5757 +421 951 82 9517 https://github.com/AndraxDev/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/andraxdev/

About me

Currently pursuing a degree in Technology at the Technical University of Košice, where I am honing my expertise with a specialization in Android and Java programming. Throughout my academic journey, I have highlighted my technical acumen and commitment to the sector by successfully initiating and completing several personal projects. My hands-on experience in these areas is a testament to my passion and potential within the field.

Experience

September 2023 – December 2023 – Developed DZS Public transport management system for SlovakTransLine, s.r.o. It includes managing drivers and vehicles, creating orders and rides, assigning drivers, managing client's database and much more.

May 2023 – September 2023 - Developed CMCChat digital assistant for elder and disable people for Michel Taal B.V.

March 2023 – present – developing SpeakGPT - a powerful open-source and low-cost ChatGPT client and mobile assistant.

January 2021 – Present – developing Teslasoft ID - a simple SSO system that allows you to use your account anywhere. Secure your account with 2FA, NfcID.

Skills

Programming languages: Java/Kotlin, Web (html/CSS/js), python, PHP, C/C++

Frameworks/tools: Android SDK, ReactJS, JWT, Firebase, Google Cloud Services, Google Play Integrity API, OpenAI API, Flask, Postman, SonarLint,

Fields: Android development, Full-stack development

Languages: Ukrainian native, English upper-intermediate (B2), Slovak upper-intermediate (B2)

Soft skills: Communication, time-management, project-management, SCRUM, Agile

Education

September 2021 – now: Bachelor's degree at Technical University of Košice in Slovakia, Intelligent Systems

February 2023 – now: CodeGym Java course

June 2022 - BEST Course: Javafication "Why your best friend is an object?"

January 2022 – May 2022 Cisco net academy "Introduction to IoT"

January 2020 - December 2020: Fundamentals of C++ course

September 2019 – June 2020: CS50's introduction to computer science (with honors)

February 2018 – May 2018: GeekSchool Python module 2 course

September 2018 – February 2018: GeekSchool Python module 1 course

January 2017 - December 2017: SoloLearn HTML/CSS/JS/JQuery/PHP